chemaxon.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Documentation - ChemAxon - DOCS

ChemAxon respects your privacy. Any personal information collected at this site will be treated with the utmost care. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, store and use the information that you provide to us online through the [www.chemaxon.com](http://www.chemaxon.com/) (the “ChemAxon Website”) or *.[chemaxon.com](http://chemaxon.com/) ("Other ChemAxon Websites") or web applications in our domains ("Web Applications") such as [chemicalize.com](http://chemicalize.com/), [chemicalize.org](http://chemicalize.org/), ("Chemicalize") and [ps-demo.chemaxon.com](https://ps-demo.chemaxon.com/) ("Plexus Suite Demo Site"), respectively (altogether collectively “ChemAxon Websites”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to other Internet sites even if accessed via ChemAxon Websites. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us in one of the ways provided below.

## What is Personal Information?

Personal information means any information from which a living individual can be identified directly, or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to their physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity.

## What Personal Information We Collect

ChemAxon collects personal information about you such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. We automatically collect other information relating to your visit to ChemAxon Websites, such as your IP address, the server into which your computer is logged on, your browser type, operating system, browser language and service provider.

## How We Collect Your Personal Information

ChemAxon obtains information from you either by you typing in your personal details or by the automatic collection of information about you as you use ChemAxon Websites.

### Keying in Your Details

If you wish to view certain sections of ChemAxon Websites, ChemAxon will ask you to key in standard personal information as you proceed through the stages of our online registration process when creating your ChemAxon Pass ([https://pass.chemaxon.com](https://pass.chemaxon.com/)).

### Automatic Collection and Cookie Policy

We use software known as cookies to facilitate navigation through ChemAxon Websites. Upon creating your ChemAxon Pass, you are assigned a unique number, which is stored in the cookie on your computer’s hard drive. The cookies help us distinguish new visitors from returning visitors and enable us to measure the electiveness of content on the ChemAxon Websites and refine that content to suit our visitor’s interests. ChemAxon cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.

You may desire cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. Some areas of our site may not function properly if you do decline to accept cookies. For more information, please review our [Cookie Policy](https://docs.chemaxon.com/display/docs/Cookie+Policy).

## What We Use Your Information For

The principle purposes for which we collect and store your personal information are to process your registration, allow you to personalize various account settings such as communication preferences, and generally maintain the user account you hold with us.

From time to time we may contact members by email with information regarding our products and services. These communications may contain information about our partners, but all emails are originated by ChemAxon. If you do not wish to receive marketing information, you can unsubscribe once you join. ChemAxon members may control their email and address information, via the ChemAxon Accounts ([https://accounts.chemaxon.com](https://accounts.chemaxon.com/)) website.

## Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly solicit or obtain individually identifying information from children under the age of 13.

## To what third parties might we transfer personal information?

We do not disclose personal information to third parties for such parties’ own marketing purposes.

We may disclose personal information to contractors and service providers acting on our behalf or under our instructions for purposes relating to the operation, maintenance, administration, improvement, and oversight of our Website and advertising services, or to fulfill individuals’ requests for information or service.

We may disclose personal information in connection with a corporate transaction, proceeding, or reorganization involving the business activities for which the information is maintained.

We may disclose personal information as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on us on ChemAxon Websites.

## How May I Review and Correct my Personal Information?

You have the right to access any identifiable personal information about you that we maintain at the time of your request. ChemAxon is committed to providing you with reasonable and practical access to your information to allow you the opportunity to identify and correct inaccuracies.

Upon creating your account you gain access to edit your personal information at any time through ChemAxon Accounts.

## How might this Privacy Policy be changed?

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so it is advisable to review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be announced on ChemAxon Websites, all amended terms shall automatically be effective [7] days after announcement.

If you have questions about our handling of personal information, you may write to us at info [at] chemaxon.com or at the addresses below.

## Corporate Identity

ChemAxon Limited is located at Záhony utca 7, Budapest, 1031 Hungary
